MUSTAFA TUFAN

mustafatufan

mustafatufan

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT PERSONAL

🤳 +90 538 018 95 16 Birthday: Nov. 13, 1992 👑

in mustafatufan Birthplace: Izmir, Turkey 🚊

Looking for a job in: Istanbul, Izmir or a remote job 🐚 Willing to relocate: Yes 🚍

Can get paid in cryptocurrency: Yes 🖔

OBJECTIVES SKILLS

➡ In 5 years: Being part of best products.

Software Development ■

In 5 years: being part of best products.
 Software Development ■
 Contract Development

SUMMARY

I am Mustafa Tufan, the software engineering graduate. I am always in pursuit of designing the best software & writing the best line of codes. I am passionate about details, continuously think how to improve myself, where I am & what I do. I always love the small piece of improvements that make products better & people's life easy. In business & socially, I believe in justice & individualism.

At the moment, I am developing with Java, J2EE, JSP, JSF, MSSQL, Sybase, Primefaces, Jasper Reports, Tomcat & Wildfly servers in Infina Software. On an average day, I am responsible to create, code & test Java beans, stored SQL procedures & functions, Primefaces JSF pages & Jasper Reports designs. I developed & published Android apps & Unity3D games in the past. I also have experience on how to use version control & project management systems. I like to use & work with high-end tech products.

I am good at puzzles, abstract thinking & logic. I like chess. I do not smoke. I am a social drinker. I watch sci-fi & fantasy movies. I love story based video games. I can not say that I am good at books but I read wiki pages a lot. My native language is Turkish, I am good at English. Also, I am learning French.

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer @ Infina

Mar. 2016 - Present

Infina is a midsize fintech company, located in Istanbul, Turkey. Currently, working in a team that develops & supports Infleks Operation project that is a back office system for investment banks. Akbank, Şekerbank & Citibank are the major users of Infleks Operation. Mainly, committing to Accounting, Fund, Derivative & Customer modules.

Entern @ Emeltek Feb. - Jun. 2015

Emeltek is a startup, launched in Elazig, Turkey. In the internship, developed & published two Android games those Rolling & Breaking Stone & KELİME BUL. with Unity3D includes Google Play Game Services, Unity Ads & Admob. Totally downloaded over 50,000.

Intern @ Netix

Jun. - Sep. 2013

Netix is a software company, located in Istanbul & Elazig, Turkey. In the internship, developed Encrypted SMS Android app which provides you send & receive SMS with AES encryption.

Android Developer @ Android Turşusu Feb. 2011 - Apr. 2013

Android Turșusu was my enterprise that includes my university & personal projects to monetize. Developed & published some Android apps & games like Bilişim Bilgi Yarışması & Afacan. All apps totally downloaded over 100,000.

Intern @ Dreamharvesters
Jun. - Sep. 2012

Dreamharvesters is a game studio, located in Antalya, Turkey. In the internship, committed to LanistaWars title. Also programmed a tool that helps to edit subtitle texts.

EDUCATION

Capital Markets & Stock Exchange @ Marmara University

2017 - 2018

2010 - 2015

3 terms non-thesis master's degree program includes finance theory, economics analysis & finance mathematics.

Software Engineering @ Firat University

8 terms software engineering bachelor's degree program includes object oriented programming, database systems, data structures, game & mobile app development, Al basics, software quality assurance & testing.

Information Technology @ Gaziemir Anadolu Technical High School 2006 - 2010

4 years high school education includes computer, programming & database basics.